onlinecasinoreviewer.com 2016-05-13

# Online Casino Reviewer Privacy Policy

## Online Casino Reviewer – Privacy Policy

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information:

 **Site Navigation  
**

Information about your computer and about your visits to and use of the Website. (Including your IP Address, Geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit and page views).

 **Cookies**

A Cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google analytics generates statistical and other information about the website by means of cookies, which are stored on users’ computers. The information relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google’s Privacy Policy is available at : [www.google.com/privacypolicy.html](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html "www.google.com/privacypolicy.html").

 **Using Your Personal Information  
**

Personal information submitted to us via this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

We may use your personal information to:

Administer the website;

  * Improve the browsing experience by personalising the website;
  * Enable your use of the services available on the website;
  * Send you email notifications which you have specifically requested;

We will not without your express consent provide your personal information to any third parties for the purpose of direct marketing.

 **Security of your Personal Information  
**

We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (Password and Firewall Protected) Servers.

 **Policy Amendments  
**

We may update this privacy policy from time to time by posting a new version on our website. Privacy Policy last amended: 24th February 2016.

Online Casino Reviewer is owned and operated by Bath Rock Media Limited, a company registered in England and Wales. Company Registration Number: 5984337.
